<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>hi</pattern>
        <template>Hello, I'm Advisorbot, your  friendly neighborhood computer science career advisor,
        what's your name?</template>
    </category>

<category><pattern>hello</pattern><template><srai>HI</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>howdy</pattern><template><srai>HI</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>sup</pattern><template><srai>HI</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>hola</pattern><template><srai>HI</srai></template></category>
    
  <category>
    <pattern>*</pattern>
    <template>I have no answer for that.</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
    <pattern>my name is *</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="name"><star/></set></think>
        Hi <get name="name"/>, I'm here to help you find a career with your computer science degree
    based on your skills, shall we begin?</template>
  </category>

  
  <category>
      <pattern>yes</pattern>
      <template>Alright! I'm gonna ask you a series of questions to determine the best career fit for you. Just pick the answer that applies most to you
        <delay>2</delay>Would you rather lead a team or work with others on a team?
        <button>
            <text>Lead a team</text>
            <postback>YesLead</postback>
        </button>
        <button>
            <text>Work with a team</text>
            <postback>NoLead</postback>
        </button>
      </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>no</pattern>
      <template>That's okay! I hope you come back another time. When you're ready, just say, "Hi"</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>YesLead</pattern>
      <template>That's great! A great leader leads to a great outcome!
        <delay>2</delay>What are you more interested in:
        <button>
            <text>Planning and Organizing</text>
            <postback>ProjectManager</postback>
        </button>
        <button>
            <text>Making sure everything works as intended</text>
            <postback>QualityAssurance</postback>
        </button>
      </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>NoLead</pattern>
      <template>That's great! Strong members of a team lead to strong outcomes!
        <delay>2</delay>What interests you more?
        <button>
            <text>Development</text>
            <postback>development</postback>
        </button>
        <button>
            <text>Analytics</text>
            <postback>analytics</postback>
        </button>
          
      </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>development</pattern>
      <template>Making things is fun and rewarding huh
        <delay>2</delay>Are you more interested in,
        <button>
            <text>How things look</text>
            <postback>frontend</postback>
        </button>
        <button>
            <text>How things work in the background</text>
            <postback>backend</postback>
        </button>
      </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>analytics</pattern>
      <template>Finding patterns in information is satisfying indeed
      <delay>2</delay>Would you say you are interested in computer security?
      <button>
          <text>Yes</text>
          <postback>SecurityAnalyst</postback>
      </button>
      <button>
          <text>No</text>
          <postback>DataAnalyst</postback>
      </button>
      </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>ProjectManager</pattern>
      <template>
          <delay>3</delay><get name="name"/>, with your answers I believe you would have great success as an IT Project Manager!
          IT Project Managers are in charge of planning, budgeting, and basically running an organization’s IT goals and initiatives. 
          <delay>5</delay>If you'd like to try again for another career recommendation, just say, "Yes." Otherwise, say, "No."
      </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>QualityAssurance</pattern>
      <template>
          <delay>3</delay><get name="name"/>, with your answers I believe you would have great success as a Quality Assurance Manager!
          Quality Assurance Managers are in charge of monitoring and ensuring high-quality standards in production, 
          inspecting processes and outputs, and supervising staff. 
          They analyze data, communicate with external officers, and maintain records.
          <delay>5</delay>If you'd like to try again for another career recommendation, just say, "Yes." Otherwise, say, "No."
      </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>frontend</pattern>
      <template>
          <delay>3</delay><get name="name"/>, with your answers I believe you'd have great success as a Front-end Software or Web developer!
          Software Developers are tasked with creating and developing websites, programs, and other applications that run on computers or other devices. 
          Web Developers are programmers that are concentrated on coding, designing, and building out the layout of a website.
          <delay>5</delay>If you'd like to try again for another career recommendation, just say, "Yes." Otherwise, say, "No."
          </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>backend</pattern>
      <template>
          <delay>3</delay><get name="name"/>, with your answers I believe you'd have great success as a Back-end Developer!
          Back-end Developers are the experts who build and maintain the mechanisms that process data and perform actions on websites. 
          Unlike front-end developers, who control everything you can see on a website, back-end developers are involved in data storage, 
          security, and other server-side functions that you cannot see.
          <delay>5</delay>If you'd like to try again for another career recommendation, just say, "Yes." Otherwise, say, "No."
      </template>
  </category>
  
  
  
  <category>
      <pattern>SecurityAnalyst</pattern>
      <template>
          <delay>3</delay><get name="name"/>, with your answers I believe you'd have great success as an Information Security Analyst!
          Information Security Analysts are in charge of implementing systems of safety and protecting a company’s computer networks.
          <delay>5</delay>If you'd like to try again for another career recommendation, just say, "Yes." Otherwise, say, "No."
      </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>DataAnalyst</pattern>
      <template>
          <delay>3</delay><get name="name"/>, with your answers I believe you'd have great success as a Data Analyst!
          A data analyst collects, cleans, and interprets data sets in order to answer a question or solve a problem. 
          They work in many industries, including business, finance, criminal justice, science, medicine, and government.
          <delay>5</delay>If you'd like to try again for another career recommendation, just say, "Yes." Otherwise, say, "No."
      </template>
  </category>

</aiml>

